scu.edu 2006-12-10

# Santa Clara University Web Site - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

This privacy statement applies to Web sites hosted on [www.scu.edu](http://www.scu.edu/).

#### Information you provide

Information about your use of the [www.scu.edu](http://www.scu.edu/) site will be recorded in the Web server access log files. The log file record does not include any personally identifiable information; we collect this data for aggregate statistics and server performance monitoring.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

#### Sharing information with others

SCU will share personally identifiable information about you when one or more of the following conditions apply:

We have your consent to share the information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
